Before I begin my questioning, I have to say this has been so deeply disturbing on a number of levels.
And what we have seen today is what we've been seeing this entire Congress,
which is an effort by my Republican colleagues and indeed some of the more extreme voices in the Republican Party
to keep Americans on a treadmill of rage.
Whatever the latest issue is that they want people to be angry about,
they do their best to keep Americans on a treadmill of rage.
And they get their Fox or Newsmax or whatever right-wing media outlet of the moment is,
they get their viewers, they get a clip from this hearing that gets displayed,
it gets put on Twitter, and they make money.
That's what all of this is all about, unfortunately.